canadiancontent.net 2011-06-04

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

**Our commitment**

     We created this privacy policy to ensure that any information obtained from our users is kept 100% confidential. We have never released any information to outside companies and never plan to. We have strong values against SPAMMERS (see Commentary about SPAM). Any users using our forum can be assured that their email address will not be given out to anybody. **Please use this privacy policy as a guarantee of our commitment to you**. 

**Your information is logged automatically**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site, and to help identify you and your shopping cart. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, and for other purposes. 

**Our site uses cookies**

Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart, and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. 

**Advertisers**

We utilise a third party agency to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies set by ads are collected by our agency, and we do not have access to this information. Our third party advertisers may collect information about your browsing habits based on this web site and other web sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the cookie program by visiting [privacy policy of our primary advertiser](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Personal Information**

Some of our services may collect and request personal information. It may include email addresses, your name(s) or surname(s), your age, birthday and other personal information. While we use this information to enhance the services we provide, we do not share any of this information with any third parties. We may, however, compile statistics based on this information from time to time. Email addresses are protected and under no circumstances are they ever shared.

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. **Canadian Content Interactive Media** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Children and the Internet**

We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children: 

  1. We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. 
  2. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent 
  3. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to: 
    1. Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes. 
    2. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification. 
    3. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity. 
  4. We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service. 
  5. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child. 
  6. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected. 
  7. We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children. 
  8. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online.
